Guide to the Harvey Reissig papers, 1969-2010.
Reissig, Harvey papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Harvey Reissig papers, 1969-2010.
22-2-4279
Harvey. Reissig
6 cubic feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, grant and consultant files, talks, reprints and slides, photographs and CDs of his research trips.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Entomology, New York State Experiment Station, Geneva and former director of Cornell's Pesticide Management Education Program (PMEP).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, grant and consultant files, talks, reprints and slides, photographs and CDs of his research trips.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Reissig, Harvey.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State College of Agriculture. Department of Entomology.; Cornell University -- Faculty.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges -- Faculty.; Entomology -- Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Research, Projects, and Assessments
Series II. Grant Files
Series III. Correspondence
Series IV. Meetings, Committees, and Conferences
Series V. Miscellaneous
Series VI. Slides
Series VII. Media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Research, Projects, and Assessments
  - Subseries Ia. General
    - Oriental Fruit Moth (OFM) Research (1 of 2), 2000-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Reports specifically on controlling the oriental fruit moth in peaches and other stone fruits
    - Oriental Fruit Moth (OFM) Research (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Female Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) Trapping, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Correspondence - Peter Landolt
    - Proposed Plan for Evalution of Reduced Risk Insecticide Programs in NY Orchards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) Parasites + Insecticides, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Summer Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Summer Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) Pheromone Trapping, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) - Transgenic McIntosh, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Apple Research + Development, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Food Quality Protection (FQPA), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - New England - Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Grant proposal
    - Entomology Research - Orchard, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Apples - Transgenic Plants, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Brazil - European Red Mites on Apples, 1992-1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Business card for entomologist from Brazil, Eduardo Humeres; travel documents for Reissig; graduate student's dissertation proposal
    - Apple Maggot Quarantines, 1996-04-1996-07 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      U.S. Apple Certification protocol for Brazil
    - New York Apple Pest Complex + Spray Schedule, 1973-03 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Sprayer Trials, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Bridging the Rift Foundation (BTR) - Project, 2000-05-15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - National Agricultural Statistics Service, USDA - Pesticide Applications - Apples, 2003-2005, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) - Outsourcing, Dogwood and Apple Orchards, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Cuban Apple Imports, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Apple Maggot Research, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Apple Maggot Control and Monitoring System Reports (1 of 2), 1983, 1998-2002, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Original manscript and revised drafts of report
    - Apple Maggot Control and Monitoring System Reports (2 of 2), 1933, 1957, 1970-1980, 1988-2001, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Records of article searches; reprints; Reissig's pre-publications
    - Apple Crop Advisory Committee (CAC), 1994-2002, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Meeting minutes; research agreement; Integrated Pest Management (IPM) related meetings; Apple Germplasm Committee related documents
    - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station (NYSAES) - Fruit Information Pool, 2003-2007, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Lists of addresses; memos between members
    - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station (NYSAES) - Hatch Project(s), 2004, 2007, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Projects on arthopod pests of apple
    - New York Integrated Fruit Protection (IFP) Protocol for Apples, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      New York's Food and Life Sciences Bulletin
    - Station Creek Mites - Data Tables, 2001-06-2001-07 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Herman Mites Data Tables and Miticide Trials, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Insect Netting, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Samples of netting; fabric samples from Apex Mills Corporation; fabric and knitting catalogs, buyer's guide, and advertisements; articles on pest management; correspondence with multiple fabric industries
    - Apple Maggot (AM) - Lab Bioassays, 1983, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Report on "Effects of Surface Residues of Azinphosmethyl on Apple Maggot Behavior, Oviposition, and Mortality," data table of apple maggots treated with Provado and sugar
    - Northeastern Integrated Pest Management - Area-Wide (AW) Mating Disruption Approach to Control Two Major Pests in New York Orchards, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Pesticide Laws and Regulations, 1993-2014, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Includes material on pesticide applicator recertification program
    - USDA RAMP Project - New York - Reduced-Risk Pest Management in Apples (2002), 2002-2003, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Handwritten notes; report; correspondence
    - USDA RAMP Project - New York - Reduced-Risk Pest Management in Apples (2005), 2004-2005, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station (NYSAES) Research Projects, 1986-1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station (NYSAES) White Paper - Task Force Report, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Department of Entomology: Strategic Plan and Study Document, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Larvae Data and Grower Contact Information, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Codling Moth Insecticide Resistance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Integrated management of insectifice resistance in France, Italy, Switzerland, Belgium, Poland, Western North America, South Africa
    - San Jose Scale (SJS), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Control of Overwintering Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) with Confirm (Insecticide), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Oblique-Banded Leafroller (OBLR) Data, 1994-2001, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Northeast Rainfed Agricultural Development - Environmental Assessment of Pesticide Use, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Sample Environmental Assessments, 1983-1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Includes Reissig's Initial Environmental Examination of Proposed Pesticide Use in the Farming Practices for Productivity Project
    - Feeding Responses of Western Corn Rootworm on Silks of Fifteen Genetic Sources of Corn, 1971-10 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      With G. E. Wilde
    - Effects of Foliage Sprays on Juvenile Hormone Analogues on Development of Draeculacephala crassicornis, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      With J. A. Kamm
    - Field Tests of Traps and Lures for the Apple Maggot, 1974-08 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Field Tests of the Response of Rhagoletis pomonella to Apples, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Reproductive Development of Adult Male D. crassicornis, 1975-01 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Effect of Synthetic Juvenile Hormone on Reproduction of Adult Male Draeculacephala crassicornis, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Performance of Apple Maggot Traps in Various Apple Tree Canopy Positions, 1975-03 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Performance of Apple Maggot Traps in Various Apple Tree Canopy Positions, 1975-08 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Evaluation of Traps for Apple Maggot in Unsprayed and Commercial Apple Orchards, 1975-08 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Marking Pheromones Deterring Repeated Oviposition in Rhagoletis Flies, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
      With R. J. Prokopy and V. Moericke
    - Comparison of Traps and Lures for Rhagoletis fausta and R. cingulata, 1976-10 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Response of the Apple Maggot, Rhagoletis pomonella, and the Cherry Fruit Fly, R. fausta, to Protein Hydrolysate Bait Sprays, 1977-02 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Published in The Canadian Entomologist
    - Capture of Released Apple Maggot Flies, Rhagoletis pomonella, on Sticky Panels, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bionomics of Rhagoletis pomonella in Crataegus, 1978-03-15 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      With D. C. Smith; published in Annals of the Entomological Society of America
    - Biology and Control of the Obliquebanded Leafroller on Apples, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Orientation Disruption of Argyrotaenia velutinana and Choristoneura rosaceana Male Moths, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      With M. Novak and W. L. Roelofs
    - Prediction of Apple Maggot Fly Emergence from Thermal Unit Accumulation, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      With J. Barnard, R. W. Weires, E. H. Glass, and R. W. Dean
    - Survival of Apple Maggot Larvae, Rhagoletis pomonella, in Picked and Unpicked Apples, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Apple Maggot Monitoring in an Apple Pest Management (PM) Program, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      With J. P. Tette; published in The Canadian Entomologist
    - Laboratory and Field Tests of Insecticides Against the Apple Maggot, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      With R. W. Weires and D. M. Soderlund; published in the Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Persistence of Four Insecticides in Controlling the Pear Psylla, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      With John R. Leeper
    - Toxicity of Several Insecticides to the Spotted Tentiform Leafmine and Its Parasite, Apanteles ornigis, 1982-08 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      With R. W. Weires, J. P. Leeper, and S. E. Lienk; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Effects of Gracillariid Leafminers on Apple Tree Growth and Production, 1982-08 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      With R. W. Weires and C. G. Forshey
    - Rates and Effect of Resurgence-Inducing Insecticides on Populations of Nilaparvata lugens and Its Predators, 1982-12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      With E. A. Heinrichs, S. Valencia, and S. Chelliah
    - Field Tests of Synthetic Apple Volatiles as Apple Maggot Attractants, 1982-12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      With B. L. Fein and W. L. Roelofs
    - Identification of Apple Volatiles Attractive to the Apple Maggot, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      With B. L. Fein and W. L. Roelofs; published in Journal of Chemical Ecology
    - Airborne Dispersal of San Jose Scale, Quadraspidiotus perniciosus, Crawlers Infesting Apple, 1983-06 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      With Diane L. Mague
    - Phenology of the San Jose Scale in New York State Apple Orchards, 1983-07 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      With Diane L. Mague; published in The Canadian Entomologist
    - Effects of Surface Residues of Azinphosmethyl on Apple Maggot Behavior, Oviposition, and Mortality, 1983-06 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      With B. H. Stanley, M. E. Valla, R. C. Seem, and J. B. Bourke
    - Management of Apple Maggot, Rhagoletis pomonella, in Disease-Resistant Dwarf and Semi-Dwarf Apple Trees, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      With R. W. Weires, C. G. Forshey, W. L. Roelofs, R. C. Lamb, H. S. Aldwinckle, and S. R. Alm
    - Insect Management in Disease-resistant Dwarf and Semi-Dwarf Apple Trees, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      With R. W. Weires, C. G. Forshey, W. L. Roelofs, R. C. Lamb, H. S. Aldwinckle
    - Timing and Effectiveness of Insecticide Treatments Against the San Jose Scale, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      With R. W. Weires, D. W. Onstad, B. H. Stanley, and D. M. Stanley; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Tests of Synthetic Apple Volatiles in Traps as Attractants for Apple Maggot Flies in Commercial Apple Orchards, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      With B. H. Stanley, W. L. Roelofs, and M. R. Schwarz
    - Monitoring Susceptibility to Azinphosmethyl in Field Populations of the Codling Moth with Pheromone Traps, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      H. Riedl, A. Seaman, and F. Henrie; published in Journal of Economic Entomology; annotations
    - Phenology and Management of the Obliquebanded Leafroller in Apple Orchards, 1985-12 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      With David W. Onstad and Christine A. Shoemaker; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Azinphosmethyl Resistance and Weight-related Response of Obliquebanded Leafroller Larvae to Insecticides, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      With B. H. Stanley and H. E. Hebding; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Influence of Apple Cultivar, Tree Phenology, and Leaf Quality on the Development and Mortality of Choristoneura rosaceana, 1986-02 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      With David W. Onstad and Christine A. Shoemaker; published in The Canadian Entomologist
    - Cyhexatin Resistance in New York Populations of European Red Mite, 1987-02 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      With C. Welty, T. J. Dennehy, and R. W. Weires; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Timing Treatments for Apple Maggot Control Using Sticky Sphere Traps Baited with Synthetic Apple Volatiles, 1987-10 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      With B. H. Stanley, W. L. Roelofs, and M. R. Schwarz, and C. A. Shoemaker
    - Control of Obliquebanded Leafroller with Chlorpyrifos, 1987-11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      With B. D. Olson and D. W. Onstad; published in Down to Earth
    - Breeding for Arthropod Resistance in Apple - Eucarpia Fruit Breeding Section Meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      With R. C. Lamb and Sarah K. Brown
    - Specificity of Olfactory Responses in the Tephritid Fruit Fly, Rhagoletis pomonella, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      With Anne L. Averill and Wendell L. Roelofs; printed in the Netherlands
    - Comparison of Residual Bioassay Methods and Criteria for Assessing Mortality of Cyhexatin-Resistant European Red Mite, 1988-04 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Susceptibility to Hexythiazox of Eggs and Larvae of European Red Mite, 1988-04 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Basing European Red Mite Control Decisions on a Census of Mites Can Save Control Costs, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      With Jan. P. Nyrop; published in New York's Food and Life Sciences Bulletin #123
    - Characterization of Resistance to Dicofol in Spider Mites from New York Apple Orchards, 1988-12 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      With T. J. Dennehy, J. P. Nyrop, and R. W. Weires; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Management of the Apple Maggot in the Eastern United States - Chapter 5, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Reprinted from Ecology and Management of Economically Important Fruit Flies
    - Activity of Clofentezine Against European Red Mite, 1989-02 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Relationship Between Field Efficacy and Laboratory Estimates of Susceptibility to Cyhexatin in Populations of European Red Mite, 1989-04 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Binomial Sequential Classification Sampling Plans for European Red Mite with Special Reference to Performance Criteria, 1989-04 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      With J. P. Nyrop and A. M. Agnello; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Stability of Cyhexatin Resistance in Field Populations of European Red Mite, 1989-06 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Relationships of Foliar Azinphosmethyl Concentration, Exposure Time, and Mortality for the Apple Maggot, 1989-06 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      With B. H. Stanley, C. A. Shoemaker, and D. S. Robson; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Development and Evaluation of a More Efficient Monitoring System for Apple Maggot, 1990-04 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      With A. M. Agnello and S. M. Spangler; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Laboratory and Field Studies of Resistance of Crab Apple Clones to Rhagoletis pomonella, 1990-06 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      With S. K. Brown, R. C. Lamb, and J. N. Cummins
    - Development and Evaluation of a Control Decision Rule for First-Generation Spotted Tentiform Leafminer in New York Apple Orchards, 1990-10 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      With J. P. Nyrop, A. M. Agnello, and J. Kovach
    - Field Measurements of Selection for European Red Mite Resistance to Dicofol in Apple Orchards, 1991-02 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      With T. E. Martinson, J. P. Nyrop, and T. J. Dennehy; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Field Measurements of Selection for Twospotted Spider Mite Resistance to Dicofol in Apple Orchards, 1991-02 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      With T. E. Martinson,T. J. Dennehy, and J. P. Nyrop; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Hexythiazox Resistance in a Field Population of European Red Mite on Apples, 1991-06 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      With L. A. Hull; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Temporal Variability in Repeated Bioassays of Field Populations of European Red Mite: Implications for Resistance Monitoring, 1991-08 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Seasonal Development and Management Strategies for Comstock Mealybug in New York Pear Orchards, 1992-02 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      With A. M. Agnello, S. M. Spangler, D. S. Lawson, and R. W. Weires; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Management of Summer Populations of European Red Mite on Apple with Horticultural Oil, 1994-02 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      With A. M. Agnello and T. Harris; published in Journal of Economic Entomology
    - Extension and Evaluation of a Simplified Monitoring Program in New York Apples, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      With Arthur M. Agnello, Joseph Kovach, Jan P. Nyrop, Deborah I. Breth, and Wayne F. Wilcox; published in American Entomologist
    - Microclimate and Columnar Apple Tree Performance within Insect-exclusionary Cages, 1994-09 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      With D. S. Lawson, S. K. Brown, and J. P. Nyrop; published in HortScience
  - Subseries Ib. Insecticide Testing and Reports, 1969-2007
    - Syngenta, Petro-Canada, Actara, Novartis, 1997-2004, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
      Precautionary statements and instructions of use; correspondence; a PowerPoint presentation; technical bulletins for other insecticides
    - Aventis and Arvesta, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      Correspondence, precautionary statements; presentation for Clutch
    - Valent Miticides, 2000-2004, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Gowan Company Development Protocol and Mesa Insecticide, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Engelhard Corporation, 1999-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Makhteshim-Agan of North America - Field Development Protocols, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      New product announcement
    - Uniroyal Chemical Protocols, 2001, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - BASF Corporation, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      Correspondence; precautionary statements
    - Exxon - Orchex, 1997-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
      Presentation; product introduction
    - FMC Corporation, 1999-03 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Rohm and Haas Company, 1998-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
      Directions for use; technical bulletin information
    - American Agricultural Services, Inc. - Makhteshim RIMON Study, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Ecogen - Correspondence, 1999-05-04 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - ELF Atochem North America - Correspondence, 1999-02-07 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - LidoChem, 1996-1998, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Zeneca Ag Products - Correspondence, Apr-May 1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Orchard 12 Treatment List and Layout, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - STLM and Aphids Treatment on Orchard 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Apple and Pear Insects Chemical Control Studies and Memorandums - K. Trammel (Extra Copies), 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Insecticides - Annual Reports - Geneva, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1976, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      Memorandum to Pesticide Industry Cooperators
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      Memorandum to Pesticide Industry Cooperators; handwritten section of report; handwritten data tables; data collection; unsent letter
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      Memorandum to members of the Pool of Information on Fruit Pests
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1982-1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1983, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 85)
      Fruit information pool members
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1990-1991, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
      Memorandum to colleagues and friends of Rick Weires
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 92)
      Each report was attached with a note asking for 120 copies
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1996-1997, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Insecticide Reports - Tests and Insect Controls on Apples and Pears, 2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fruit Insect and Mite Control Studies - Eastern New York - Weires, 1977-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Subseries Ic. Abroad
    - Composition Notebooks - Brazil, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Composition Notebooks - Romania and Slovakia, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Composition Notebooks - Armenia, ADB - Pesticides, 1986, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes on pesticide manufacturers; includes notes on Department of Agricultural Chemistry at Beijing Agricultural University
    - International Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1999-11 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Correspondence; proposed distance leanring pesticide resistance module